<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on LING WEIYUE&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on LING WEIYUE&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 20:21:42 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Architecture in Huaxi Campus</title>
      <link>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/huaxi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 20:21:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/huaxi/</guid>
      <description>I visited Hua&amp;rsquo;xi campus this Sunday to attend the research group’s meeting. As I have never visited there before (as I have to stay at Jiang&amp;rsquo;an campus for all four years!), some helpful team member volunteered to show us around.
I really love those quaint-looking architecture in Hua&amp;rsquo;xi campus (also in Wang&amp;rsquo;jiang campus), while cannot be experienced here.
This is the most iconic building in Huaxi - the Bell Tower, which also can be seen on our student card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waffles &amp; Milk Tea</title>
      <link>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/waffle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 17:08:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/waffle/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s really unfortunate that there rarely have coffee &amp;amp; dessert shops around the Jiang&amp;rsquo;an campus.
Recently, I came across a nice little shop, but not to my surprise, it takes an hour by bus to get there from school. Well, all right, even though the location is also in Shuangliu District, it&amp;rsquo;s still miles away.
I ordered a pudding and waffle combo——Okay, no pudding——the pudding is replaced by ice cream. Beyond my expectations, the waffle, along with fruits and cream, is very delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Night Safari Adventure</title>
      <link>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/night/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 14:03:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/night/</guid>
      <description>In front of me is a mass of blackness, with dense and ever-changing tree shadows. It seems there are a few strange bird calls, accompanied by hoarse growls, by my ears, and I’m unsure of where they come. Suddenly, it becomes quiet again, causing my heart to tighten, and my steps seem to hesitate. This is what I felt of entering Night Safari after dusk, and these feelings are novel and unforgettable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of &#34;My Octopus Teacher&#34;</title>
      <link>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/my-octopus-teacher/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 15:50:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/my-octopus-teacher/</guid>
      <description>It is a serendipitous surprise that I met this film, or rather, documentary, and it soon touched my heart deeply. Now, I’m eager to write this review to look back at the good time spent with it. Actually, it’s the third time I watch the documentary, but still I couldn’t hold back tears.
All it tells is about the story between the photographer and octopus. Following the protagonist Craig Foster, also the film-maker, I dive into the clear waters, weaving through lush kelp forests.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
