<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on LING WEIYUE&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on LING WEIYUE&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 18:13:29 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Approaching Harvest Season</title>
      <link>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/harvest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 18:13:29 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/harvest/</guid>
      <description>I haven&amp;rsquo;t been back to my hometown during National Day for some years.
Unlike the winter scenery I often see when I go back, now it is a vibrant autumn view. Some beautiful wildflowers are still blooming, the sky is clear blue, and as far as eyes can see, it is still a sea of green. Of course, the most prominent view is the vast expanse of paddy fields (Oryza sativa) with rice approaching maturity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Folk Customs·Wedding</title>
      <link>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/wedding/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 18:13:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/wedding/</guid>
      <description>Recently, my brother is getting married, and we are helping with the preparations and participating in the wedding.
In this modern era, traditional folk customs and practices have indeed been simplified to a great extent and are no longer too strict. However, some unique characteristics are still preserved. It is worth highlighting that the entire process has now been significantly compressed in terms of time, so it can be finished within a day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pure Darkness</title>
      <link>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/dark/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 18:13:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/dark/</guid>
      <description>It gets dark early in the evening in the countryside. Although geographically speaking, the time for darkness to fall in cities and suburbs should be similar, here you will feel that darkness comes early.
When I go out for some fresh air after finishing dinner - it is before 7 o&amp;rsquo;clock - I suddenly encounter dense darkness, realizing that this is a very different experience. Although both Sichuan and Jiangsu provinces use Beijing time, there exists some difference in the actual time due to the gap in longitude and other factors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annual Dinner</title>
      <link>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/dinner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 13:52:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/dinner/</guid>
      <description>[Due to privacy concerns, I have added some mosaic effects.]
It&amp;rsquo;s a truly precious opportunity to dinner have a gathering once a year with fellow-villager. Because Jiangsu and Sichuan Province are far apart, spanning across a large portion of China, it&amp;rsquo;s natural that there aren&amp;rsquo;t many people from Jiangsu Province studying here in Chengdu. Therefore, it is awesome for us to gather two or three tables together every year. Therefore, I’m very grateful to several generations of active organizers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exotic Pet</title>
      <link>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/pet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 20:03:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/pet/</guid>
      <description>Today, I lost one side of the earphone&amp;rsquo;s cover, so I went to a offline store. To my disappointment, they didn&amp;rsquo;t do anything and just told me to search on Taobao. In the end, as expected, I found it on Taobao. Taobao is truly amazing! After solving this, I came cross a marketplace selling many lovely and beautiful trinkets. But I was attracted by a stand which sells a lot of kinds of pets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Architecture in Huaxi Campus</title>
      <link>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/huaxi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 20:21:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/huaxi/</guid>
      <description>I visited Hua&amp;rsquo;xi campus this Sunday to attend the research group’s meeting. As I have never visited there before (as I have to stay at Jiang&amp;rsquo;an campus for all four years!), some helpful team member volunteered to show us around.
I really love those quaint-looking architecture in Hua&amp;rsquo;xi campus (also in Wang&amp;rsquo;jiang campus), while cannot be experienced here.
This is the most iconic building in Huaxi - the Bell Tower, which also can be seen on our student card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waffles &amp; Milk Tea</title>
      <link>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/waffle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 17:08:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/waffle/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s really unfortunate that there rarely have coffee &amp;amp; dessert shops around the Jiang&amp;rsquo;an campus.
Recently, I came across a nice little shop, but not to my surprise, it takes an hour by bus to get there from school. Well, all right, even though the location is also in Shuangliu District, it&amp;rsquo;s still miles away.
I ordered a pudding and waffle combo——Okay, no pudding——the pudding is replaced by ice cream. Beyond my expectations, the waffle, along with fruits and cream, is very delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scenery of Beijing</title>
      <link>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/beijing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 20:23:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/beijing/</guid>
      <description>When I went to Tsinghua University to attend a summer camp, I took the opportunity to visit some of Beijing&amp;rsquo;s attractions in just a few days. The last time I came to Beijing was when I had just learned how to walk, so I don&amp;rsquo;t have any lasting memories of this city.
Although didn&amp;rsquo;t have the opportunity to attend Tsinghua University, it is still a great experience to be led by Tsinghua’s senior schoolmate on a tour of the campus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Night Safari Adventure</title>
      <link>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/night/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 14:03:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/night/</guid>
      <description>In front of me is a mass of blackness, with dense and ever-changing tree shadows. It seems there are a few strange bird calls, accompanied by hoarse growls, by my ears, and I’m unsure of where they come. Suddenly, it becomes quiet again, causing my heart to tighten, and my steps seem to hesitate. This is what I felt of entering Night Safari after dusk, and these feelings are novel and unforgettable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of &#34;My Octopus Teacher&#34;</title>
      <link>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/my-octopus-teacher/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 15:50:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodrian-blog.github.io/posts/my-octopus-teacher/</guid>
      <description>It is a serendipitous surprise that I met this film, or rather, documentary, and it soon touched my heart deeply. Now, I’m eager to write this review to look back at the good time spent with it. Actually, it’s the third time I watch the documentary, but still I couldn’t hold back tears.
All it tells is about the story between the photographer and octopus. Following the protagonist Craig Foster, also the film-maker, I dive into the clear waters, weaving through lush kelp forests.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
